{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127826866","data":{"timestamp":" 947127826866"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127839350","data":{"timestamp":" 947127839350"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127840514","data":{"timestamp":" 947127840514"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127841398","data":{"timestamp":" 947127841398"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127842472","data":{"timestamp":" 947127842472"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127843476","data":{"timestamp":" 947127843476"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZOEA"," userResponse":" ALIZOEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127844330","data":{"timestamp":" 947127844330"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWEKA"," userResponse":" KUMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127845424","data":{"timestamp":" 947127845424"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKILALIA"," userResponse":" AKILALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127846078","data":{"timestamp":" 947127846078"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127847362","data":{"timestamp":" 947127847362"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" MARIDADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127849924","data":{"timestamp":" 947127849924"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127850107","data":{"timestamp":" 947127850107"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127851071","data":{"timestamp":" 947127851071"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEKEE"," userResponse":" KIPEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127852434","data":{"timestamp":" 947127852434"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULITENGEZWA"," userResponse":" ULITENGEZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127852578","data":{"timestamp":" 947127852578"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127853721","data":{"timestamp":" 947127853721"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZIYE"," userResponse":" SHANGAZIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127854364","data":{"timestamp":" 947127854364"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127855449","data":{"timestamp":" 947127855448"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127856233","data":{"timestamp":" 947127856233"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127856346","data":{"timestamp":" 947127856345"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127857029","data":{"timestamp":" 947127857029"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTENDE"," userResponse":" MTENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127860018","data":{"timestamp":" 947127860018"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127860883","data":{"timestamp":" 947127860882"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127861105","data":{"timestamp":" 947127861105"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127861719","data":{"timestamp":" 947127861719"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127861833","data":{"timestamp":" 947127861833"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127862826","data":{"timestamp":" 947127862826"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WARIDI"," userResponse":" WARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127863726","data":{"timestamp":" 947127863725"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLUU"," userResponse":" BLUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127864426","data":{"timestamp":" 947127864425"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127865689","data":{"timestamp":" 947127865689"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANIKIWITI"," userResponse":" CHANIKIWITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127868300","data":{"timestamp":" 947127868300"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127869341","data":{"timestamp":" 947127869340"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127869545","data":{"timestamp":" 947127869545"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127870260","data":{"timestamp":" 947127870259"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKEKA"," userResponse":" MIKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127871267","data":{"timestamp":" 947127871267"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGINE"," userResponse":" MINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127872264","data":{"timestamp":" 947127872263"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127873013","data":{"timestamp":" 947127873013"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127873609","data":{"timestamp":" 947127873609"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127874468","data":{"timestamp":" 947127874468"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127874982","data":{"timestamp":" 947127874982"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127875829","data":{"timestamp":" 947127875829"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127879267","data":{"timestamp":" 947127879267"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127879960","data":{"timestamp":" 947127879959"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127880767","data":{"timestamp":" 947127880767"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127881914","data":{"timestamp":" 947127881913"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127882571","data":{"timestamp":" 947127882570"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127883214","data":{"timestamp":" 947127883214"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" SEHEMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127883908","data":{"timestamp":" 947127883908"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAVU"," userResponse":" KAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127884836","data":{"timestamp":" 947127884835"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127885709","data":{"timestamp":" 947127885708"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127885942","data":{"timestamp":" 947127885942"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127887226","data":{"timestamp":" 947127887226"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOJAA"," userResponse":" ILIYOJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127887810","data":{"timestamp":" 947127887810"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWE"," userResponse":" MAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127890429","data":{"timestamp":" 947127890429"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127890762","data":{"timestamp":" 947127890762"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127891496","data":{"timestamp":" 947127891496"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGE"," userResponse":" NGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127893140","data":{"timestamp":" 947127893140"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127893613","data":{"timestamp":" 947127893613"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127894116","data":{"timestamp":" 947127894116"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127894599","data":{"timestamp":" 947127894599"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127897788","data":{"timestamp":" 947127897788"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127898442","data":{"timestamp":" 947127898442"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127899885","data":{"timestamp":" 947127899885"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWAHI"," userResponse":" HAKUWAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127900487","data":{"timestamp":" 947127900487"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMWA"," userResponse":" UMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127901060","data":{"timestamp":" 947127901060"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127901734","data":{"timestamp":" 947127901733"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIUMBE"," userResponse":" VIUMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127902148","data":{"timestamp":" 947127902148"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127903141","data":{"timestamp":" 947127903141"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATARI"," userResponse":" HATARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127906178","data":{"timestamp":" 947127906178"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127907162","data":{"timestamp":" 947127907162"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127908154","data":{"timestamp":" 947127908154"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127908668","data":{"timestamp":" 947127908668"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127908842","data":{"timestamp":" 947127908842"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127910064","data":{"timestamp":" 947127910064"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEKEE"," userResponse":" KIPEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127911468","data":{"timestamp":" 947127911468"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAMKINGA"," userResponse":" UNAMKINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127911710","data":{"timestamp":" 947127911710"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127912835","data":{"timestamp":" 947127912834"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATARI"," userResponse":" HATARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127913398","data":{"timestamp":" 947127913398"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOYOTE"," userResponse":" YOYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127916398","data":{"timestamp":" 947127916398"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127917351","data":{"timestamp":" 947127917351"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127918074","data":{"timestamp":" 947127918074"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127918966","data":{"timestamp":" 947127918966"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEREVU"," userResponse":" MWEREVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127921974","data":{"timestamp":" 947127921974"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127922726","data":{"timestamp":" 947127922726"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJUA"," userResponse":" KUJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127923409","data":{"timestamp":" 947127923409"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127924122","data":{"timestamp":" 947127924122"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIMA"," userResponse":" KISIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127924365","data":{"timestamp":" 947127924365"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127925089","data":{"timestamp":" 947127925089"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127926472","data":{"timestamp":" 947127926472"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKOKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127929698","data":{"timestamp":" 947127929698"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJUA"," userResponse":" ALIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127930481","data":{"timestamp":" 947127930481"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127931243","data":{"timestamp":" 947127931243"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYATTA"," userResponse":" MANYATTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127931426","data":{"timestamp":" 947127931426"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127932439","data":{"timestamp":" 947127932439"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYAKE"," userResponse":" NYANYAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127933263","data":{"timestamp":" 947127933263"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127935634","data":{"timestamp":" 947127935634"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127935876","data":{"timestamp":" 947127935876"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127936540","data":{"timestamp":" 947127936540"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127937630","data":{"timestamp":" 947127937630"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIENDA"," userResponse":" ALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127937793","data":{"timestamp":" 947127937792"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127937863","data":{"timestamp":" 947127937863"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a992d5d1-84f1-4bfd-b95a-074d3c0456fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIENDA"," userResponse":" ALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127947974","data":{"timestamp":" 947127947974"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KALAMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" KALAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127953846","data":{"timestamp":" 947127953846"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KALAMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" KALAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127955465","data":{"timestamp":" 947127955465"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIBOKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127958316","data":{"timestamp":" 947127958315"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIBOKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127959917","data":{"timestamp":" 947127959917"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KICHWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127962480","data":{"timestamp":" 947127962480"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KICHWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127964078","data":{"timestamp":" 947127964077"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIJIKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" KIJIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127966981","data":{"timestamp":" 947127966980"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIJIKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" KIJIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127968589","data":{"timestamp":" 947127968589"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITENGE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" KITENGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127973865","data":{"timestamp":" 947127973865"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITENGE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127975428","data":{"timestamp":" 947127975428"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" KITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127979553","data":{"timestamp":" 947127979552"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127981159","data":{"timestamp":" 947127981159"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIPEPEO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEPEO"," userResponse":" KIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127983961","data":{"timestamp":" 947127983960"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIPEPEO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEPEO"," userResponse":" KIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127987111","data":{"timestamp":" 947127987110"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIKOMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127993831","data":{"timestamp":" 947127993830"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIKOMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127995440","data":{"timestamp":" 947127995440"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOFIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127998069","data":{"timestamp":" 947127998068"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOFIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947127999641","data":{"timestamp":" 947127999640"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUCHAKURO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHAKURO"," userResponse":" KUCHAKURO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128004072","data":{"timestamp":" 947128004072"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUCHAKURO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHAKURO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128005677","data":{"timestamp":" 947128005677"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KONDOO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128008675","data":{"timestamp":" 947128008674"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KONDOO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128010258","data":{"timestamp":" 947128010258"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUNDI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNDI"," userResponse":" KUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128013118","data":{"timestamp":" 947128013118"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUNDI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNDI"," userResponse":" KUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128014729","data":{"timestamp":" 947128014729"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOMBE"," userResponse":" KOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128018391","data":{"timestamp":" 947128018391"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128019988","data":{"timestamp":" 947128019988"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KINYOZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" KINYOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128023134","data":{"timestamp":" 947128023133"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KINYOZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" KINYOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128024690","data":{"timestamp":" 947128024690"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAROTI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128028125","data":{"timestamp":" 947128028125"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAROTI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" START_KAROTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128031335","data":{"timestamp":" 947128031335"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAROTI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128032963","data":{"timestamp":" 947128032962"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITABU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" KITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128037323","data":{"timestamp":" 947128037323"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITABU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128038933","data":{"timestamp":" 947128038932"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128041522","data":{"timestamp":" 947128041522"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128043093","data":{"timestamp":" 947128043093"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUTEMBEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128050131","data":{"timestamp":" 947128050130"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUTEMBEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128051722","data":{"timestamp":" 947128051722"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KWAHERI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAHERI"," userResponse":" KWAHERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128059372","data":{"timestamp":" 947128059372"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KWAHERI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAHERI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128060992","data":{"timestamp":" 947128060992"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128069614","data":{"timestamp":" 947128069614"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128071272","data":{"timestamp":" 947128071272"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITUNGUU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUNGUU"," userResponse":" KITUNGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128074398","data":{"timestamp":" 947128074398"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITUNGUU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUNGUU"," userResponse":" KITUNGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128075963","data":{"timestamp":" 947128075963"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KATIKATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128078350","data":{"timestamp":" 947128078350"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KATIKATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" START_KATIKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128082150","data":{"timestamp":" 947128082150"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KATIKATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" START_KATIKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128083748","data":{"timestamp":" 947128083748"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KATIKATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128085343","data":{"timestamp":" 947128085343"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUNI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128090925","data":{"timestamp":" 947128090925"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUNI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128092571","data":{"timestamp":" 947128092570"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITAMBAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITAMBAA"," userResponse":" KITAMBAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128099790","data":{"timestamp":" 947128099789"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITAMBAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITAMBAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128101396","data":{"timestamp":" 947128101396"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUSOMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128107737","data":{"timestamp":" 947128107736"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUSOMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128109361","data":{"timestamp":" 947128109360"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KINU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINU"," userResponse":" KINU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128111852","data":{"timestamp":" 947128111852"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KINU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINU"," userResponse":" KINU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128113461","data":{"timestamp":" 947128113460"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KILIMANJARO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIMANJARO"," userResponse":" KILIMANJARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128118960","data":{"timestamp":" 947128118959"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KILIMANJARO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIMANJARO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128120560","data":{"timestamp":" 947128120559"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIATU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIATU"," userResponse":" KIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128125534","data":{"timestamp":" 947128125532"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIATU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128127106","data":{"timestamp":" 947128127106"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUKU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128130534","data":{"timestamp":" 947128130534"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUKU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128132117","data":{"timestamp":" 947128132116"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128135660","data":{"timestamp":" 947128135660"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128137669","data":{"timestamp":" 947128137668"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" KULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128137830","data":{"timestamp":" 947128137830"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128165703","data":{"timestamp":" 947128165702"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" KULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128176023","data":{"timestamp":" 947128176022"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 24ad2daa-190a-4a3d-9e7a-2ad2cd9008a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" KULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128190174","data":{"timestamp":" 947128190173"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128191069","data":{"timestamp":" 947128191069"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128191730","data":{"timestamp":" 947128191729"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128191955","data":{"timestamp":" 947128191955"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128192655","data":{"timestamp":" 947128192654"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128192999","data":{"timestamp":" 947128192999"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128193501","data":{"timestamp":" 947128193501"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128196501","data":{"timestamp":" 947128196501"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128196825","data":{"timestamp":" 947128196825"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128197439","data":{"timestamp":" 947128197439"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128198634","data":{"timestamp":" 947128198634"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAPENDANA"," userResponse":" TUNAPENDANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128199419","data":{"timestamp":" 947128199418"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128202215","data":{"timestamp":" 947128202215"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukitumwa tunaenda pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKITUMWA"," userResponse":" TUKITUMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128203187","data":{"timestamp":" 947128203186"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukitumwa tunaenda pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAENDA"," userResponse":" TUNAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128203982","data":{"timestamp":" 947128203981"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukitumwa tunaenda pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128206902","data":{"timestamp":" 947128206901"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128207359","data":{"timestamp":" 947128207359"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128208216","data":{"timestamp":" 947128208215"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILITUMWA"," userResponse":" NILITUMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128208841","data":{"timestamp":" 947128208840"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUKANI"," userResponse":" DUKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128208998","data":{"timestamp":" 947128208998"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128209486","data":{"timestamp":" 947128209485"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128209880","data":{"timestamp":" 947128209880"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128211514","data":{"timestamp":" 947128211514"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKANUNUE"," userResponse":" NIKANUNUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128212304","data":{"timestamp":" 947128212303"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMVI"," userResponse":" CHUMVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128212829","data":{"timestamp":" 947128212829"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128213559","data":{"timestamp":" 947128213558"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAFUTA"," userResponse":" MAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128216335","data":{"timestamp":" 947128216334"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilienda na Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIENDA"," userResponse":" NILIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128216587","data":{"timestamp":" 947128216587"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilienda na Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128217134","data":{"timestamp":" 947128217133"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilienda na Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128220071","data":{"timestamp":" 947128220071"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKIWA"," userResponse":" TUKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128221014","data":{"timestamp":" 947128221013"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128222141","data":{"timestamp":" 947128222140"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIWAONA"," userResponse":" TULIWAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128222748","data":{"timestamp":" 947128222747"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128223637","data":{"timestamp":" 947128223636"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZETU"," userResponse":" WENZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128224894","data":{"timestamp":" 947128224894"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHEZA"," userResponse":" WAKICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128225429","data":{"timestamp":" 947128225428"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128225607","data":{"timestamp":" 947128225607"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128226131","data":{"timestamp":" 947128226130"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128228868","data":{"timestamp":" 947128228867"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nilitamani sana kucheza mpira huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128230232","data":{"timestamp":" 947128230232"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nilitamani sana kucheza mpira huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILITAMANI"," userResponse":" NILITAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128230876","data":{"timestamp":" 947128230875"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nilitamani sana kucheza mpira huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128231511","data":{"timestamp":" 947128231510"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nilitamani sana kucheza mpira huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128232090","data":{"timestamp":" 947128232090"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nilitamani sana kucheza mpira huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128232273","data":{"timestamp":" 947128232272"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nilitamani sana kucheza mpira huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128235269","data":{"timestamp":" 947128235268"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpira!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILISEMA"," userResponse":" NILISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128236072","data":{"timestamp":" 947128236072"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpira!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AH"," userResponse":" AH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128239521","data":{"timestamp":" 947128239520"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpira!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128243059","data":{"timestamp":" 947128243058"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" NILIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128243601","data":{"timestamp":" 947128243600"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128244845","data":{"timestamp":" 947128244845"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWENDE"," userResponse":" TWENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128245614","data":{"timestamp":" 947128245613"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUWAOMBE"," userResponse":" TUWAOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128246239","data":{"timestamp":" 947128246238"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128246654","data":{"timestamp":" 947128246653"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAO"," userResponse":" NAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128247612","data":{"timestamp":" 947128247611"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128250096","data":{"timestamp":" 947128250095"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128250759","data":{"timestamp":" 947128250758"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUPENDA"," userResponse":" HUPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128251383","data":{"timestamp":" 947128251383"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128251603","data":{"timestamp":" 947128251603"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128252314","data":{"timestamp":" 947128252313"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128255257","data":{"timestamp":" 947128255256"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128256290","data":{"timestamp":" 947128256290"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALINIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128257416","data":{"timestamp":" 947128257416"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWENDE"," userResponse":" TWENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128257914","data":{"timestamp":" 947128257913"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128258778","data":{"timestamp":" 947128258778"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUKANI"," userResponse":" DUKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128259544","data":{"timestamp":" 947128259543"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128260043","data":{"timestamp":" 947128260043"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TURUDI"," userResponse":" TURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128260679","data":{"timestamp":" 947128260678"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128263829","data":{"timestamp":" 947128263829"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini nilimwambia Chuma Tucheze kwanza wewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128264683","data":{"timestamp":" 947128264683"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini nilimwambia Chuma Tucheze kwanza wewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" NILIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128265169","data":{"timestamp":" 947128265169"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini nilimwambia Chuma Tucheze kwanza wewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128266294","data":{"timestamp":" 947128266294"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini nilimwambia Chuma Tucheze kwanza wewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUCHEZE"," userResponse":" TUCHEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128266858","data":{"timestamp":" 947128266857"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini nilimwambia Chuma Tucheze kwanza wewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128267358","data":{"timestamp":" 947128267357"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini nilimwambia Chuma Tucheze kwanza wewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128270090","data":{"timestamp":" 947128270090"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukienda nyumbani nyanya hataturuhusu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKIENDA"," userResponse":" TUKIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128270893","data":{"timestamp":" 947128270893"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukienda nyumbani nyanya hataturuhusu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128271617","data":{"timestamp":" 947128271617"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukienda nyumbani nyanya hataturuhusu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128272943","data":{"timestamp":" 947128272943"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukienda nyumbani nyanya hataturuhusu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATATURUHUSU"," userResponse":" HATATURUHUSU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128276735","data":{"timestamp":" 947128276735"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikubaliwa na wenzetu tukacheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIKUBALIWA"," userResponse":" TULIKUBALIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128276946","data":{"timestamp":" 947128276946"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikubaliwa na wenzetu tukacheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128277813","data":{"timestamp":" 947128277812"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikubaliwa na wenzetu tukacheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZETU"," userResponse":" WENZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128279017","data":{"timestamp":" 947128279017"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikubaliwa na wenzetu tukacheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKACHEZA"," userResponse":" TUKACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128279589","data":{"timestamp":" 947128279588"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikubaliwa na wenzetu tukacheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128282729","data":{"timestamp":" 947128282728"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa golikipa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" NILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128283754","data":{"timestamp":" 947128283753"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa golikipa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOLIKIPA"," userResponse":" GOLIKIPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128288049","data":{"timestamp":" 947128288048"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijitahidi kudaka mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIJITAHIDI"," userResponse":" NILIJITAHIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128288853","data":{"timestamp":" 947128288852"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijitahidi kudaka mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUDAKA"," userResponse":" KUDAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128289468","data":{"timestamp":" 947128289468"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijitahidi kudaka mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128292187","data":{"timestamp":" 947128292187"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzangu hawakuweza kufunga goli hata moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZANGU"," userResponse":" WENZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128293153","data":{"timestamp":" 947128293153"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzangu hawakuweza kufunga goli hata moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128293759","data":{"timestamp":" 947128293759"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzangu hawakuweza kufunga goli hata moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFUNGA"," userResponse":" KUFUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128294243","data":{"timestamp":" 947128294242"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzangu hawakuweza kufunga goli hata moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOLI"," userResponse":" GOLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128294957","data":{"timestamp":" 947128294956"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzangu hawakuweza kufunga goli hata moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128295430","data":{"timestamp":" 947128295430"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzangu hawakuweza kufunga goli hata moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128298509","data":{"timestamp":" 947128298509"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uwanja tuliochezea ulikuwa na mchanga mwingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWANJA"," userResponse":" UWANJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128299871","data":{"timestamp":" 947128299871"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uwanja tuliochezea ulikuwa na mchanga mwingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIOCHEZEA"," userResponse":" TULIOCHEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128301066","data":{"timestamp":" 947128301066"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uwanja tuliochezea ulikuwa na mchanga mwingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128301289","data":{"timestamp":" 947128301289"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uwanja tuliochezea ulikuwa na mchanga mwingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128302112","data":{"timestamp":" 947128302112"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uwanja tuliochezea ulikuwa na mchanga mwingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHANGA"," userResponse":" MCHANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128303254","data":{"timestamp":" 947128303254"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uwanja tuliochezea ulikuwa na mchanga mwingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGI"," userResponse":" MWINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128305904","data":{"timestamp":" 947128305903"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magoli yake yalikuwa mawe makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGOLI"," userResponse":" MAGOLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128306677","data":{"timestamp":" 947128306677"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magoli yake yalikuwa mawe makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128307292","data":{"timestamp":" 947128307291"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magoli yake yalikuwa mawe makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIKUWA"," userResponse":" YALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128307889","data":{"timestamp":" 947128307889"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magoli yake yalikuwa mawe makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWE"," userResponse":" MAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128308755","data":{"timestamp":" 947128308755"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magoli yake yalikuwa mawe makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" MAKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128311574","data":{"timestamp":" 947128311574"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128311787","data":{"timestamp":" 947128311787"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128312651","data":{"timestamp":" 947128312651"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHEZO"," userResponse":" MCHEZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128313710","data":{"timestamp":" 947128313709"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIENDA"," userResponse":" TULIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128314516","data":{"timestamp":" 947128314516"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUKANI"," userResponse":" DUKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128315310","data":{"timestamp":" 947128315310"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128315997","data":{"timestamp":" 947128315996"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATUKUWA"," userResponse":" HATUKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128316200","data":{"timestamp":" 947128316199"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128316766","data":{"timestamp":" 947128316766"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128319606","data":{"timestamp":" 947128319606"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIANZA"," userResponse":" NILIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128320589","data":{"timestamp":" 947128320589"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128323420","data":{"timestamp":" 947128323419"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128324715","data":{"timestamp":" 947128324714"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINIKEMEA"," userResponse":" ALINIKEMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128325719","data":{"timestamp":" 947128325718"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ACHA"," userResponse":" ACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128326211","data":{"timestamp":" 947128326211"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128328239","data":{"timestamp":" 947128328238"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128328698","data":{"timestamp":" 947128328698"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128329426","data":{"timestamp":" 947128329425"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULITAKA"," userResponse":" ULITAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128330038","data":{"timestamp":" 947128330037"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUCHEZE"," userResponse":" TUCHEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128330594","data":{"timestamp":" 947128330594"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABLA"," userResponse":" KABLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128330753","data":{"timestamp":" 947128330752"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128331146","data":{"timestamp":" 947128331146"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128331817","data":{"timestamp":" 947128331817"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUKANI"," userResponse":" DUKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128334664","data":{"timestamp":" 947128334663"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulirudi nyumbani bila chumvi wala mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIRUDI"," userResponse":" TULIRUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128335649","data":{"timestamp":" 947128335648"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulirudi nyumbani bila chumvi wala mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128336011","data":{"timestamp":" 947128336011"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulirudi nyumbani bila chumvi wala mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128336848","data":{"timestamp":" 947128336848"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulirudi nyumbani bila chumvi wala mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMVI"," userResponse":" CHUMVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128337627","data":{"timestamp":" 947128337626"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulirudi nyumbani bila chumvi wala mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" WALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128338544","data":{"timestamp":" 947128338544"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulirudi nyumbani bila chumvi wala mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAFUTA"," userResponse":" MAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128341232","data":{"timestamp":" 947128341231"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikuwa tumechafuka kweli kweli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128342489","data":{"timestamp":" 947128342489"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikuwa tumechafuka kweli kweli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMECHAFUKA"," userResponse":" TUMECHAFUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128343167","data":{"timestamp":" 947128343166"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikuwa tumechafuka kweli kweli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWELI"," userResponse":" KWELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128343621","data":{"timestamp":" 947128343620"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikuwa tumechafuka kweli kweli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWELI"," userResponse":" KWELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128347013","data":{"timestamp":" 947128347013"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulimkuta nyanya amekasirika mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIMKUTA"," userResponse":" TULIMKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128347474","data":{"timestamp":" 947128347474"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulimkuta nyanya amekasirika mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128349101","data":{"timestamp":" 947128349100"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulimkuta nyanya amekasirika mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEKASIRIKA"," userResponse":" AMEKASIRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128349552","data":{"timestamp":" 947128349551"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulimkuta nyanya amekasirika mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128351953","data":{"timestamp":" 947128351953"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SWALI"," userResponse":" SWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128352090","data":{"timestamp":" 947128352089"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128352593","data":{"timestamp":" 947128352592"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128353631","data":{"timestamp":" 947128353630"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITUULIZA"," userResponse":" ALITUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128354330","data":{"timestamp":" 947128354330"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128355611","data":{"timestamp":" 947128355610"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMEKUWA"," userResponse":" MMEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128356075","data":{"timestamp":" 947128356074"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128356494","data":{"timestamp":" 947128356494"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128356645","data":{"timestamp":" 947128356644"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128357788","data":{"timestamp":" 947128357788"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128361459","data":{"timestamp":" 947128361458"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" ALIPOGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128361901","data":{"timestamp":" 947128361900"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128362977","data":{"timestamp":" 947128362976"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPOTEZA"," userResponse":" TULIPOTEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128363661","data":{"timestamp":" 947128363661"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELA"," userResponse":" HELA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128365160","data":{"timestamp":" 947128365160"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128366987","data":{"timestamp":" 947128366986"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWASAMEHE"," userResponse":" NAWASAMEHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128367263","data":{"timestamp":" 947128367262"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128368542","data":{"timestamp":" 947128368542"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128369404","data":{"timestamp":" 947128369403"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSIRUDIE"," userResponse":" MSIRUDIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128369951","data":{"timestamp":" 947128369950"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128370998","data":{"timestamp":" 947128370997"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128371425","data":{"timestamp":" 947128371424"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128372002","data":{"timestamp":" 947128372002"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUHUSA"," userResponse":" RUHUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128375098","data":{"timestamp":" 947128375097"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulienda haraka kuwalisha kuku na bata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIENDA"," userResponse":" TULIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128375854","data":{"timestamp":" 947128375854"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulienda haraka kuwalisha kuku na bata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128376790","data":{"timestamp":" 947128376789"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulienda haraka kuwalisha kuku na bata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALISHA"," userResponse":" KUWALISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128377245","data":{"timestamp":" 947128377245"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulienda haraka kuwalisha kuku na bata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128377438","data":{"timestamp":" 947128377438"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulienda haraka kuwalisha kuku na bata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128377881","data":{"timestamp":" 947128377881"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulienda haraka kuwalisha kuku na bata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" BATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128381118","data":{"timestamp":" 947128381117"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128382208","data":{"timestamp":" 947128382207"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIOGA"," userResponse":" TULIOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128382410","data":{"timestamp":" 947128382410"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128382815","data":{"timestamp":" 947128382814"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128383900","data":{"timestamp":" 947128383900"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAFI"," userResponse":" WASAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128386594","data":{"timestamp":" 947128386592"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128386723","data":{"timestamp":" 947128386722"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 0e2e476e-1b8f-49f6-802c-b9d61ef05c30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAFI"," userResponse":" WASAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128398431","data":{"timestamp":" 947128398430"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 60186c71-61de-4b93-9d01-56f789180793"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_D-K-R"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128400349","data":{"timestamp":" 947128400348"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 60186c71-61de-4b93-9d01-56f789180793"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_K_D-K-R"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128411839","data":{"timestamp":" 947128411839"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 60186c71-61de-4b93-9d01-56f789180793"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_K_D-K-R"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128420373","data":{"timestamp":" 947128420373"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 60186c71-61de-4b93-9d01-56f789180793"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_K_D-K-R"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128430012","data":{"timestamp":" 947128430012"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128430814","data":{"timestamp":" 947128430814"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128431007","data":{"timestamp":" 947128431007"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128431651","data":{"timestamp":" 947128431651"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWA"," userResponse":" MIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128432622","data":{"timestamp":" 947128432621"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128433399","data":{"timestamp":" 947128433399"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128434243","data":{"timestamp":" 947128434243"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128434505","data":{"timestamp":" 947128434504"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128435183","data":{"timestamp":" 947128435183"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128435867","data":{"timestamp":" 947128435866"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128438282","data":{"timestamp":" 947128438281"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128438827","data":{"timestamp":" 947128438827"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128440066","data":{"timestamp":" 947128440065"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOZAA"," userResponse":" ALIPOZAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128440831","data":{"timestamp":" 947128440830"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128441518","data":{"timestamp":" 947128441518"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128442570","data":{"timestamp":" 947128442569"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFARIKI"," userResponse":" ALIFARIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128445856","data":{"timestamp":" 947128445855"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UCHUNGU"," userResponse":" UCHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128445991","data":{"timestamp":" 947128445991"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128446953","data":{"timestamp":" 947128446952"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFILIWA"," userResponse":" KUFILIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128447155","data":{"timestamp":" 947128447154"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128447799","data":{"timestamp":" 947128447799"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128448333","data":{"timestamp":" 947128448333"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128449744","data":{"timestamp":" 947128449743"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMFANYA"," userResponse":" ULIMFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128450447","data":{"timestamp":" 947128450446"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128451238","data":{"timestamp":" 947128451238"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128452338","data":{"timestamp":" 947128452338"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128452539","data":{"timestamp":" 947128452539"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128453129","data":{"timestamp":" 947128453129"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128455549","data":{"timestamp":" 947128455548"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128456141","data":{"timestamp":" 947128456141"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128457040","data":{"timestamp":" 947128457039"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128458095","data":{"timestamp":" 947128458094"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIRUKIA"," userResponse":" AKIRUKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128458657","data":{"timestamp":" 947128458657"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAWI"," userResponse":" TAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128459389","data":{"timestamp":" 947128459389"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128460283","data":{"timestamp":" 947128460282"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128460844","data":{"timestamp":" 947128460844"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128461863","data":{"timestamp":" 947128461862"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINGINE"," userResponse":" LINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128463215","data":{"timestamp":" 947128463215"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPIGA"," userResponse":" AKIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128464244","data":{"timestamp":" 947128464243"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128465539","data":{"timestamp":" 947128465538"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWI"," userResponse":" KWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128468912","data":{"timestamp":" 947128468911"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128469830","data":{"timestamp":" 947128469830"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128470153","data":{"timestamp":" 947128470152"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128470856","data":{"timestamp":" 947128470855"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128471789","data":{"timestamp":" 947128471788"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128472751","data":{"timestamp":" 947128472750"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128475181","data":{"timestamp":" 947128475181"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128475743","data":{"timestamp":" 947128475742"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128477186","data":{"timestamp":" 947128477185"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMZIDI"," userResponse":" ULIMZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128478046","data":{"timestamp":" 947128478046"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASWA"," userResponse":" HASWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128479553","data":{"timestamp":" 947128479553"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOWAONA"," userResponse":" ALIPOWAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128480708","data":{"timestamp":" 947128480708"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKINA"," userResponse":" AKINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128481269","data":{"timestamp":" 947128481269"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128481946","data":{"timestamp":" 947128481946"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128482545","data":{"timestamp":" 947128482544"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128482752","data":{"timestamp":" 947128482752"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128483348","data":{"timestamp":" 947128483347"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128483852","data":{"timestamp":" 947128483852"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128487080","data":{"timestamp":" 947128487080"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128487593","data":{"timestamp":" 947128487592"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128488382","data":{"timestamp":" 947128488381"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128490051","data":{"timestamp":" 947128490050"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128490707","data":{"timestamp":" 947128490707"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128490921","data":{"timestamp":" 947128490920"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128491142","data":{"timestamp":" 947128491142"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128495203","data":{"timestamp":" 947128495203"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128495671","data":{"timestamp":" 947128495670"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128496282","data":{"timestamp":" 947128496282"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAWI"," userResponse":" TAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128496986","data":{"timestamp":" 947128496985"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128497269","data":{"timestamp":" 947128497268"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128497798","data":{"timestamp":" 947128497798"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILE"," userResponse":" LILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128500579","data":{"timestamp":" 947128500578"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128502051","data":{"timestamp":" 947128502050"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIPITA"," userResponse":" ZILIPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128502424","data":{"timestamp":" 947128502424"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128503187","data":{"timestamp":" 947128503187"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128504047","data":{"timestamp":" 947128504046"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZIDI"," userResponse":" ALIZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128504902","data":{"timestamp":" 947128504901"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128505707","data":{"timestamp":" 947128505707"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128508907","data":{"timestamp":" 947128508907"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alizaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128510381","data":{"timestamp":" 947128510380"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alizaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZAA"," userResponse":" ALIZAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128510959","data":{"timestamp":" 947128510959"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alizaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128513945","data":{"timestamp":" 947128513944"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMUA"," userResponse":" ALIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128514933","data":{"timestamp":" 947128514932"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPELEKA"," userResponse":" KUMPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128515554","data":{"timestamp":" 947128515554"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128516048","data":{"timestamp":" 947128516047"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128516953","data":{"timestamp":" 947128516953"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128517842","data":{"timestamp":" 947128517841"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128518464","data":{"timestamp":" 947128518464"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPITA"," userResponse":" WAPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128518940","data":{"timestamp":" 947128518940"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128520057","data":{"timestamp":" 947128520056"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMWONE"," userResponse":" WAMWONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128520502","data":{"timestamp":" 947128520501"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128521521","data":{"timestamp":" 947128521520"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTAKIA"," userResponse":" KUMTAKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128522133","data":{"timestamp":" 947128522132"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERI"," userResponse":" HERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128525366","data":{"timestamp":" 947128525366"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128526268","data":{"timestamp":" 947128526268"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHUKA"," userResponse":" ALISHUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128526540","data":{"timestamp":" 947128526540"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128527404","data":{"timestamp":" 947128527404"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWEKA"," userResponse":" KUMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128528049","data":{"timestamp":" 947128528049"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTOWE"," userResponse":" MTOTOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128529015","data":{"timestamp":" 947128529014"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128531660","data":{"timestamp":" 947128531658"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128532214","data":{"timestamp":" 947128532214"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128533396","data":{"timestamp":" 947128533395"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" MWINDAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128534280","data":{"timestamp":" 947128534279"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128535355","data":{"timestamp":" 947128535355"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIREJEA"," userResponse":" AKIREJEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128536240","data":{"timestamp":" 947128536240"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128539288","data":{"timestamp":" 947128539287"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONA"," userResponse":" ALIMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128539970","data":{"timestamp":" 947128539970"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128540172","data":{"timestamp":" 947128540171"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128541029","data":{"timestamp":" 947128541028"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128541861","data":{"timestamp":" 947128541861"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKILALA"," userResponse":" AKILALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128542437","data":{"timestamp":" 947128542436"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANDO"," userResponse":" KANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128542641","data":{"timestamp":" 947128542640"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128543166","data":{"timestamp":" 947128543166"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128546598","data":{"timestamp":" 947128546597"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" MWINDAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128547901","data":{"timestamp":" 947128547900"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMBEBA"," userResponse":" ALIMBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128548846","data":{"timestamp":" 947128548846"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128549626","data":{"timestamp":" 947128549626"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128550252","data":{"timestamp":" 947128550251"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128550824","data":{"timestamp":" 947128550822"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128551391","data":{"timestamp":" 947128551390"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128554281","data":{"timestamp":" 947128554281"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128555367","data":{"timestamp":" 947128555366"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128556450","data":{"timestamp":" 947128556449"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128556895","data":{"timestamp":" 947128556894"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128557543","data":{"timestamp":" 947128557542"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" WATATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128558895","data":{"timestamp":" 947128558895"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" WALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128559749","data":{"timestamp":" 947128559749"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWONA"," userResponse":" KUMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128560289","data":{"timestamp":" 947128560289"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128561047","data":{"timestamp":" 947128561047"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128564114","data":{"timestamp":" 947128564114"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" WATATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128564574","data":{"timestamp":" 947128564574"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128565732","data":{"timestamp":" 947128565732"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIIMBA"," userResponse":" WALIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128566789","data":{"timestamp":" 947128566788"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128567741","data":{"timestamp":" 947128567740"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128570243","data":{"timestamp":" 947128570243"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe chini!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128571415","data":{"timestamp":" 947128571414"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe chini!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128573960","data":{"timestamp":" 947128573959"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128574686","data":{"timestamp":" 947128574685"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128577466","data":{"timestamp":" 947128577466"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128578539","data":{"timestamp":" 947128578538"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128580943","data":{"timestamp":" 947128580942"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128581940","data":{"timestamp":" 947128581940"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128583170","data":{"timestamp":" 947128583169"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUSHWA"," userResponse":" ALIRUSHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128584432","data":{"timestamp":" 947128584431"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128584843","data":{"timestamp":" 947128584843"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128585717","data":{"timestamp":" 947128585717"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128586345","data":{"timestamp":" 947128586345"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128587159","data":{"timestamp":" 947128587159"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128590459","data":{"timestamp":" 947128590459"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128591021","data":{"timestamp":" 947128591021"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128592528","data":{"timestamp":" 947128592528"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOENDELEA"," userResponse":" WALIPOENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128593280","data":{"timestamp":" 947128593279"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128593489","data":{"timestamp":" 947128593488"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128593923","data":{"timestamp":" 947128593922"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128594835","data":{"timestamp":" 947128594835"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128596025","data":{"timestamp":" 947128596025"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128597158","data":{"timestamp":" 947128597158"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128597901","data":{"timestamp":" 947128597901"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTINI"," userResponse":" MTINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128598104","data":{"timestamp":" 947128598103"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128599134","data":{"timestamp":" 947128599134"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANGALIA"," userResponse":" KUANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128602139","data":{"timestamp":" 947128602138"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOGOPA"," userResponse":" ALIOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128602708","data":{"timestamp":" 947128602708"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128603487","data":{"timestamp":" 947128603486"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128604042","data":{"timestamp":" 947128604042"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128605222","data":{"timestamp":" 947128605221"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128606186","data":{"timestamp":" 947128606186"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEFARIKI"," userResponse":" ANGEFARIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128606684","data":{"timestamp":" 947128606684"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128607505","data":{"timestamp":" 947128607504"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128610550","data":{"timestamp":" 947128610549"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128611189","data":{"timestamp":" 947128611189"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128611400","data":{"timestamp":" 947128611399"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128612428","data":{"timestamp":" 947128612428"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" MWINDAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128613456","data":{"timestamp":" 947128613456"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAONA"," userResponse":" ALIWAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128614271","data":{"timestamp":" 947128614271"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128615465","data":{"timestamp":" 947128615465"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHEZA"," userResponse":" WAKICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128615795","data":{"timestamp":" 947128615794"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128616781","data":{"timestamp":" 947128616780"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128617437","data":{"timestamp":" 947128617436"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128620515","data":{"timestamp":" 947128620515"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAONYA"," userResponse":" ALIWAONYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128621811","data":{"timestamp":" 947128621810"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128622889","data":{"timestamp":" 947128622889"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAANGALIFU"," userResponse":" WAANGALIFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128625281","data":{"timestamp":" 947128625281"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128625804","data":{"timestamp":" 947128625803"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLETE"," userResponse":" MLETE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128626385","data":{"timestamp":" 947128626384"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128630143","data":{"timestamp":" 947128630143"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHUKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIMCHUKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128630579","data":{"timestamp":" 947128630579"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128631272","data":{"timestamp":" 947128631272"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128632091","data":{"timestamp":" 947128632091"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKONONI"," userResponse":" MIKONONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128632701","data":{"timestamp":" 947128632700"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128633265","data":{"timestamp":" 947128633265"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128634479","data":{"timestamp":" 947128634479"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMBARIKI"," userResponse":" KUMBARIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128638171","data":{"timestamp":" 947128638170"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWEKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128638643","data":{"timestamp":" 947128638642"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128639356","data":{"timestamp":" 947128639356"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128640085","data":{"timestamp":" 947128640085"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128641140","data":{"timestamp":" 947128641139"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128642184","data":{"timestamp":" 947128642184"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128642537","data":{"timestamp":" 947128642536"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128643346","data":{"timestamp":" 947128643346"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128646291","data":{"timestamp":" 947128646291"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMBEBA"," userResponse":" ALIMBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128647154","data":{"timestamp":" 947128647153"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAWE"," userResponse":" MWANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128648352","data":{"timestamp":" 947128648351"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFUANI"," userResponse":" KIFUANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128648576","data":{"timestamp":" 947128648576"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128649351","data":{"timestamp":" 947128649350"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128650244","data":{"timestamp":" 947128650243"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTINI"," userResponse":" MTINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128652935","data":{"timestamp":" 947128652934"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128653043","data":{"timestamp":" 947128653043"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTINI"," userResponse":" MTINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128665878","data":{"timestamp":" 947128665877"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 62f46ead-94f6-423a-9903-004f43a65a96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128680522","data":{"timestamp":" 947128680522"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" fa3daa25-6b76-4d50-8c09-8c7d9f5e0b4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128681547","data":{"timestamp":" 947128681547"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" fa3daa25-6b76-4d50-8c09-8c7d9f5e0b4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128682143","data":{"timestamp":" 947128682143"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" fa3daa25-6b76-4d50-8c09-8c7d9f5e0b4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128682782","data":{"timestamp":" 947128682782"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" fa3daa25-6b76-4d50-8c09-8c7d9f5e0b4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128684151","data":{"timestamp":" 947128684151"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" fa3daa25-6b76-4d50-8c09-8c7d9f5e0b4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128685101","data":{"timestamp":" 947128685101"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" fa3daa25-6b76-4d50-8c09-8c7d9f5e0b4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128686294","data":{"timestamp":" 947128686294"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" fa3daa25-6b76-4d50-8c09-8c7d9f5e0b4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128687033","data":{"timestamp":" 947128687033"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" fa3daa25-6b76-4d50-8c09-8c7d9f5e0b4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128691201","data":{"timestamp":" 947128691201"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" fa3daa25-6b76-4d50-8c09-8c7d9f5e0b4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128693301","data":{"timestamp":" 947128693301"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" fa3daa25-6b76-4d50-8c09-8c7d9f5e0b4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128698602","data":{"timestamp":" 947128698601"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" fa3daa25-6b76-4d50-8c09-8c7d9f5e0b4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128703667","data":{"timestamp":" 947128703667"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" fa3daa25-6b76-4d50-8c09-8c7d9f5e0b4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128709330","data":{"timestamp":" 947128709330"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" fa3daa25-6b76-4d50-8c09-8c7d9f5e0b4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128715009","data":{"timestamp":" 947128715009"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" fa3daa25-6b76-4d50-8c09-8c7d9f5e0b4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128720536","data":{"timestamp":" 947128720536"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" fa3daa25-6b76-4d50-8c09-8c7d9f5e0b4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128725728","data":{"timestamp":" 947128725728"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" fa3daa25-6b76-4d50-8c09-8c7d9f5e0b4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128731071","data":{"timestamp":" 947128731071"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" fa3daa25-6b76-4d50-8c09-8c7d9f5e0b4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128733037","data":{"timestamp":" 947128733036"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" fa3daa25-6b76-4d50-8c09-8c7d9f5e0b4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ND_1v5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128744865","data":{"timestamp":" 947128744865"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 4e9ae484-5c1b-4a05-a381-d052cc41499c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_K-J-P"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128749231","data":{"timestamp":" 947128749231"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 4e9ae484-5c1b-4a05-a381-d052cc41499c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_K-W-H"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128754370","data":{"timestamp":" 947128754370"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 4e9ae484-5c1b-4a05-a381-d052cc41499c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_K-A-V"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128757629","data":{"timestamp":" 947128757628"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 4e9ae484-5c1b-4a05-a381-d052cc41499c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_K_K-A-V"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129189440","data":{"timestamp":" 947129189439"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 4e9ae484-5c1b-4a05-a381-d052cc41499c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_K_K-A-V"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129189524","data":{"timestamp":" 947129189524"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a373130a-2e8d-488b-b5ce-aec394937675"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129200867","data":{"timestamp":" 947129200867"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129205326","data":{"timestamp":" 947129205326"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129209863","data":{"timestamp":" 947129209863"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129214524","data":{"timestamp":" 947129214524"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129218340","data":{"timestamp":" 947129218340"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129222723","data":{"timestamp":" 947129222723"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129227393","data":{"timestamp":" 947129227393"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129236809","data":{"timestamp":" 947129236808"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129242177","data":{"timestamp":" 947129242176"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129247385","data":{"timestamp":" 947129247385"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129254087","data":{"timestamp":" 947129254087"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129258631","data":{"timestamp":" 947129258631"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129265763","data":{"timestamp":" 947129265763"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129271655","data":{"timestamp":" 947129271655"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129280870","data":{"timestamp":" 947129280870"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129285532","data":{"timestamp":" 947129285532"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129291315","data":{"timestamp":" 947129291315"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129296331","data":{"timestamp":" 947129296330"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129302771","data":{"timestamp":" 947129302771"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129307627","data":{"timestamp":" 947129307627"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129313874","data":{"timestamp":" 947129313874"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129318815","data":{"timestamp":" 947129318815"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129331080","data":{"timestamp":" 947129331080"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129335641","data":{"timestamp":" 947129335641"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129339671","data":{"timestamp":" 947129339671"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129345443","data":{"timestamp":" 947129345442"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129353465","data":{"timestamp":" 947129353465"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129359853","data":{"timestamp":" 947129359852"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129367056","data":{"timestamp":" 947129367055"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129531667","data":{"timestamp":" 947129531666"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" d7f45a67-f03e-4dd8-8aca-7f036b83b368"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129531746","data":{"timestamp":" 947129531746"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 4368d091-8a93-4d08-9455-43966e603312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilifikiria juu ya rangi ya machungwa siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZIMA"," userResponse":" NZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129539176","data":{"timestamp":" 947129539176"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" 4368d091-8a93-4d08-9455-43966e603312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nilifikiria juu ya rangi ya machungwa siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129550343","data":{"timestamp":" 947129550342"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129552511","data":{"timestamp":" 947129552510"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129554633","data":{"timestamp":" 947129554633"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129557834","data":{"timestamp":" 947129557833"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129560081","data":{"timestamp":" 947129560081"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129562342","data":{"timestamp":" 947129562342"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129565236","data":{"timestamp":" 947129565236"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129567482","data":{"timestamp":" 947129567481"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129569680","data":{"timestamp":" 947129569680"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129572927","data":{"timestamp":" 947129572926"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129575036","data":{"timestamp":" 947129575036"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129577133","data":{"timestamp":" 947129577133"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129580088","data":{"timestamp":" 947129580088"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129582334","data":{"timestamp":" 947129582333"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129584592","data":{"timestamp":" 947129584591"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129587655","data":{"timestamp":" 947129587655"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129590026","data":{"timestamp":" 947129590026"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129592381","data":{"timestamp":" 947129592381"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129595411","data":{"timestamp":" 947129595410"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129597577","data":{"timestamp":" 947129597576"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129599741","data":{"timestamp":" 947129599740"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129602858","data":{"timestamp":" 947129602858"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129605042","data":{"timestamp":" 947129605041"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129607234","data":{"timestamp":" 947129607234"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129610452","data":{"timestamp":" 947129610452"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129612882","data":{"timestamp":" 947129612881"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129615321","data":{"timestamp":" 947129615320"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129618488","data":{"timestamp":" 947129618487"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129620810","data":{"timestamp":" 947129620810"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129623077","data":{"timestamp":" 947129623077"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129626080","data":{"timestamp":" 947129626080"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129628309","data":{"timestamp":" 947129628309"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129630525","data":{"timestamp":" 947129630525"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129633482","data":{"timestamp":" 947129633482"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129635869","data":{"timestamp":" 947129635868"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129638232","data":{"timestamp":" 947129638232"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129641340","data":{"timestamp":" 947129641340"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129643661","data":{"timestamp":" 947129643661"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129646008","data":{"timestamp":" 947129646008"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129649031","data":{"timestamp":" 947129649029"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129651316","data":{"timestamp":" 947129651316"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129653579","data":{"timestamp":" 947129653579"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129656832","data":{"timestamp":" 947129656832"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129659123","data":{"timestamp":" 947129659123"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129661386","data":{"timestamp":" 947129661385"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129664752","data":{"timestamp":" 947129664752"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129667242","data":{"timestamp":" 947129667241"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129669683","data":{"timestamp":" 947129669683"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129672566","data":{"timestamp":" 947129672566"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129674779","data":{"timestamp":" 947129674777"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129676982","data":{"timestamp":" 947129676981"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129680427","data":{"timestamp":" 947129680426"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129682755","data":{"timestamp":" 947129682755"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129685102","data":{"timestamp":" 947129685102"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129688258","data":{"timestamp":" 947129688258"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129690531","data":{"timestamp":" 947129690530"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129692783","data":{"timestamp":" 947129692783"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129695832","data":{"timestamp":" 947129695832"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129697986","data":{"timestamp":" 947129697985"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129700138","data":{"timestamp":" 947129700137"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129703272","data":{"timestamp":" 947129703271"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129705528","data":{"timestamp":" 947129705527"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129707820","data":{"timestamp":" 947129707819"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129711092","data":{"timestamp":" 947129711091"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129713292","data":{"timestamp":" 947129713291"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129715516","data":{"timestamp":" 947129715512"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129718818","data":{"timestamp":" 947129718818"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129721204","data":{"timestamp":" 947129721203"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129723571","data":{"timestamp":" 947129723570"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129726653","data":{"timestamp":" 947129726652"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129729024","data":{"timestamp":" 947129729023"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129731374","data":{"timestamp":" 947129731374"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129734769","data":{"timestamp":" 947129734768"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129734879","data":{"timestamp":" 947129734879"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129747582","data":{"timestamp":" 947129747582"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129755959","data":{"timestamp":" 947129755959"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129765036","data":{"timestamp":" 947129765036"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000106_060322"," gameId":" a6c57b1e-4b14-4323-8768-fce4de4c05b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}